{
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": "151",
      "question": "A company wants to migrate its on-premises data center to A WS. A ccording to the company's compliance requirements, the company can use only the ap-northeast-3 Region. Company administrators are not permitted to connect VPCs to the internet. Which solutions will meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "options": {
        "A": "Use A WS Control Tower to implement data residency guardrails to deny internet access and deny access to all A WS Regions except ap- northeast-3.",
        "B": "Use rules in A WS WAF to prevent internet access. Deny access to all A WS Regions except ap-northeast-3 in the A WS account settings.",
        "C": "Use A WS Organizations to conFigure service control policies (SCPS) that prevent VPCs from gaining internet access. Deny access to all A WS Regions except ap-northeast-3.",
        "D": "Create an outbound rule for the network A CL in each VPC to deny all traffic from 0.0.0.0/0. Create an IAM policy for each user to prevent the use of any A WS Region other than ap-northeast-3.",
        "E": "Use A WS ConFig to activate managed rules to detect and alert for internet gateways and to detect and alert for new resources deployed outside of ap-northeast-3."
      },
      "correct_answer": "AC",
      "explanation": "A. Use A WS Control Tower to implement data residency guardrails to deny internet access and deny access to all A WS Regions except ap- northeast-3.\nC. Use A WS Organizations to configure service control policies (SCPs) that prevent VPCs from gaining internet access. Deny access to all A WS Regions except ap-northeast-3."
    },
    {
      "id": "152",
      "question": "A company uses a three-tier web application to provide training to new employees. The application is accessed for only 12 hours every day. The company is using an A mazon RDS for MySQL DB instance to store information and wants to minimize costs. What should A solutions architect do to meet these requirements?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Configure an IAM policy for A WS Systems Manager Session Manager. Create an IAM role for the policy. Update the trust relationship of the role. Set up automatic start and stop for the DB instance.",
        "B": "Create an A mazon ElastiCache for Redis cache cluster that gives users the ability to access the data from the cache when the DB instance is stopped. Invalidate the cache after the DB instance is started.",
        "C": "Launch an A mazon EC2 instance. Create an IAM role that grants access to A mazon RDS. A ttach the role to the EC2 instance. Configure a cron job to start and stop the EC2 instance on the desired schedule.",
        "D": "Create A WS Lambda functions to start and stop the DB instance. Create A mazon EventBridge (A mazon CloudWatch Events) scheduled rules to invoke the Lambda functions. Configure the Lambda functions as event targets for the rules."
      },
      "correct_answer": "D",
      "explanation": "Create A WS Lambda functions to start and stop the DB instance. Create A mazon EventBridge (A mazon CloudWatch Events) scheduled rules to invoke the Lambda functions. Configure the Lambda functions as event targets for the rules."
    },
    {
      "id": "153",
      "question": "A company sells ringtones created from clips of popular songs. The files containing the ringtones are stored in A mazon S3 Standard and are at least 128 KB in size. The company has millions of files, but downloads are infrequent for ringtones older than 90 days. The company needs to save money on storage while keeping the most accessed files readily available for its users. Which action should the company take to meet these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Configure S3 Standard-Infrequent A ccess (S3 Standard-IA) storage for the initial storage tier of the objects.",
        "B": "Move the files to S3 Intelligent-Tiering and conFigure it to move objects to a less expensive storage tier after 90 days.",
        "C": "Configure S3 inventory to manage objects and move them to S3 Standard-Infrequent A ccess (S3 Standard-1A) after 90 days.",
        "D": "Implement an S3 Lifecycle policy that moves the objects from S3 Standard to S3 Standard-Infrequent A ccess (S3 Standard-1A) after 90 days."
      },
      "correct_answer": "D",
      "explanation": "Implement an S3 Lifecycle policy that moves the objects from S3 Standard to S3 Standard-Infrequent A ccess (S3 Standard-1A) after 90 days."
    },
    {
      "id": "154",
      "question": "A company needs to save the results from amedical trial to an A mazon S3 repository. The repository must allow afew scientists to add new files and must restrict all other users to read-only access. No users can have the ability to modify or delete any files in the repository. The company must keep every File in the repository for aminimum of 1 year after its creation date. Which solution will meet these requirements?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Use S3 Object Lock in governance mode with a legal hold of 1 year.",
        "B": "Use S3 Object Lock in compliance mode with a retention period of 365 days.",
        "C": "Use an IAM role to restrict all users from deleting or changing objects in the S3 bucket. Use an S3 bucket policy to only allow the IAM role.",
        "D": "Configure the S3 bucket to invoke an A WS Lambda function every time an object is added. Configure the function to track the hash of the saved object so that modiFied objects can be marked accordingly."
      },
      "correct_answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Use S3 Object Lock in compliance mode with a retention period of 365 days."
    },
    {
      "id": "155",
      "question": "A large media company hosts a web application on A WS. The company wants to start caching confidential media files so that users around the world will have reliable access to the files. The content is stored in A mazon S3 buckets. The company must deliver the content quickly, regardless of where the requests originate geographically. Which solution will meet these requirements?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Use A WS DataSync to connect the S3 buckets to the web application.",
        "B": "Deploy A WS Global A ccelerator to connect the S3 buckets to the web application.",
        "C": "Deploy A mazon CloudFront to connect the S3 buckets to CloudFront edge servers.",
        "D": "Use A mazon Simple Queue Service (A mazon SQS) to connect the S3 buckets to the web application."
      },
      "correct_answer": "C",
      "explanation": "Deploy A mazon CloudFront to connect the S3 buckets to CloudFront edge servers."
    },
    {
      "id": "156",
      "question": "A company produces batch data that comes from different databases. The company also produces live stream data from network sensors and application A PIs. The company needs to consolidate all the data into one place for business analytics. The company needs to process the incoming data and then stage the data in different A mazon S3 buckets. Teams will later run one-time queries and import the data into abusiness intelligence tool to show key performance indicators (KPIs). Which combination of steps will meet these requirements with the LEAST operational overhead? (Choose two.)",
      "options": {
        "A": "Use A mazon A thena for one-time queries. Use A mazon QuickSight to create dashboards for KPIs.",
        "B": "Use A mazon Kinesis Data A nalytics for one-time queries. Use A mazon QuickSight to create dashboards for KPIs.",
        "C": "Create custom A WS Lambda functions to move the individual records from the databases to an A mazon Redshift cluster.",
        "D": "Use an A WS Glue extract, transform, and load (ETL) job to convert the data into JSON format. Load the data into multiple A mazon OpenSearch Service (A mazon Elasticsearch Service) clusters.",
        "E": "Use blueprints in A WS Lake Formation to identify the data that can be ingested into a data lake. Use A WS Glue to crawl the source, extract the data, and load the data into A mazon S3 in A pache Parquet format."
      },
      "correct_answer": "AC",
      "explanation": "A.  A mazon A thena for one-time queries. Use A mazon QuickSight to create dashboards for KPIs.\nC. Create custom A WS Lambda functions to move the individual records from the databases to an A mazon Redshift cluster."
    },
    {
      "id": "157",
      "question": "A company stores data in an A mazon A urora PostgreSQL DB cluster. The company must store all the data for 5 years and must delete all the data after 5 years. The company also must indefinitely keep audit logs of actions that are performed within the database. Currently, the company has automated backups configured for A urora. Which combination of steps should A solutions architect take to meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "options": {
        "A": "Take a manual snapshot of the DB cluster.",
        "B": "Create a lifecycle policy for the automated backups.",
        "C": "Configure automated backup retention for 5 years.",
        "D": "Configure an A mazon CloudWatch Logs export for the DB cluster.",
        "E": "Use A WS Backup to take the backups and to keep the backups for 5 years."
      },
      "correct_answer": "DE",
      "explanation": "D. Configure an A mazon CloudWatch Logs export for the DB cluster.\nE. Use A WS Backup to take the backups and to keep the backups for 5 years."
    },
    {
      "id": "158",
      "question": "A solutions architect is optimizing a website for an upcoming musical event. Videos of the performances will be streamed in real time and then will be available on demand. The event is expected to attract aglobal online audience. Which service will improve the performance of both the real-time and on-demand streaming?",
      "options": {
        "A": "A mazon CloudFront",
        "B": "A WS Global A ccelerator",
        "C": "A mazon Route 53",
        "D": "A mazon S3 Transfer A cceleration"
      },
      "correct_answer": "B",
      "explanation": "A solutions architect is optimizing a website for an upcoming musical event. Videos of the performances will be streamed in real time and then will be available on demand. The event is expected to attract a global online audience.\n\nWhich service will improve the performance of both the real-time and on-demand streaming?\n A. A mazon CloudFront\nB. A WS Global A ccelerator"
    },
    {
      "id": "159",
      "question": "A company is running a publicly accessible serverless application that uses A mazon A PI Gateway and A WS Lambda. The application\u2019s traffic recently spiked due to fraudulent requests from botnets. Which steps should A solutions architect take to block requests from unauthorized users? (Choose two.)",
      "options": {
        "A": "Create a usage plan with an A PI key that is shared with genuine users only.",
        "B": "Integrate logic within the Lambda function to ignore the requests from fraudulent IP addresses.",
        "C": "Implement an A WS WAF rule to target malicious requests and trigger actions to Filter them out.",
        "D": "Convert the existing public A PI to a private A PI. Update the DNS records to redirect users to the new A PI endpoint.",
        "E": "Create an IAM role for each user attempting to access the A PI. A user will assume the role when making the A PI call."
      },
      "correct_answer": "AC",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "160",
      "question": "A n ecommerce company hosts its analytics application in the A WS Cloud. The application generates about 300 MB of data each month. The data is stored in JSON format. The company is evaluating adisaster recovery solution to back up the data. The data must be accessible in milliseconds if it is needed, and the data must be kept for 30 days. Which solution meets these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "options": {
        "A": "A mazon OpenSearch Service (A mazon Elasticsearch Service)",
        "B": "A mazon S3 Glacier",
        "C": "A mazon S3 Standard",
        "D": "A mazon RDS for PostgreSQL"
      },
      "correct_answer": "A",
      "explanation": "A n ecommerce company hosts its analytics application in the A WS Cloud. The application generates about 300 MB of data each month. The data is stored in JSON format. The company is evaluating a disaster recovery solution to back up the data. The data must be accessible in milliseconds if it is needed, and the data must be kept for 30 days.\n\nWhich solution meets these requirements MOST cost-effectively? \n\n    A. A mazon OpenSearch Service (A mazon Elasticsearch Service)\n    B. A mazon S3 Glacier\n    C. A mazon S3 Standard\n    D. A mazon RDS for PostgreSQL"
    },
    {
      "id": "161",
      "question": "A company has asmall Python application that processes JSON documents and outputs the results to an on-premises SQL database. The application runs thousands of times each day. The company wants to move the application to the A WS Cloud. The company needs a highly available solution that maximizes scalability and minimizes operational overhead. Which solution will meet these requirements?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Place the JSON documents in an A mazon S3 bucket. Run the Python code on multiple A mazon EC2 instances to process the documents. Store the results in an A mazon A urora DB cluster.",
        "B": "Place the JSON documents in an A mazon S3 bucket. Create an A WS Lambda function that runs the Python code to process the documents as they arrive in the S3 bucket. Store the results in an A mazon A urora DB cluster.",
        "C": "Place the JSON documents in an A mazon Elastic Block Store (A mazon EBS) volume. Use the EBS Multi-A ttach feature to attach the volume to multiple A mazon EC2 instances. Run the Python code on the EC2 instances to process the documents. Store the results on an A mazon RDS DB instance.",
        "D": "Place the JSON documents in an A mazon Simple Queue Service (A mazon SQS) queue as messages. Deploy the Python code as a container on an A mazon Elastic Container Service (A mazon ECS) cluster that is conFigured with the A mazon EC2 launch type. Use the container to process the SQS messages. Store the results on an A mazon RDS DB instance."
      },
      "correct_answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Place the JSON documents in an A mazon S3 bucket. Create an A WS Lambda function that runs the Python code to process the documents as they arrive in the S3 bucket. Store the results in an A mazon A urora DB cluster."
    },
    {
      "id": "162",
      "question": "A company wants to use high performance computing (HPC) infrastructure on A WS for Financial risk modeling. The company\u2019s HPC workloads run on Linux. Each HPC workflow runs on hundreds of A mazon EC2 Spot Instances, is short-lived, and generates thousands of output files that are ultimately stored in persistent storage for analytics and long-term future use. The company seeks acloud storage solution that permits the copying of on-premises data to long-term persistent storage to make data available for processing by all EC2 instances. The solution should also be a high performance file system that is integrated with persistent storage to read and write datasets and output files. Which combination of A WS services meets these requirements?",
      "options": {
        "A": "A mazon FSx for Lustre integrated with A mazon S3",
        "B": "A mazon FSx for Windows File Server integrated with A mazon S3",
        "C": "A mazon S3 Glacier integrated with A mazon Elastic Block Store (A mazon EBS)",
        "D": "A mazon S3 bucket with a VPC endpoint integrated with an A mazon Elastic Block Store (A mazon EBS) General Purpose SSD (gp2) volume"
      },
      "correct_answer": "A",
      "explanation": "A mazon FSx for Lustre integrated with A mazon S3"
    },
    {
      "id": "163",
      "question": "A company is building acontainerized application on premises and decides to move the application to A WS. The application will have thousands of users soon after it is deployed. The company is unsure how to manage the deployment of containers at scale. The company needs to deploy the containerized application in a highly available architecture that minimizes operational overhead. Which solution will meet these requirements?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Store container images in an A mazon Elastic Container Registry (A mazon ECR) repository. Use an A mazon Elastic Container Service (A mazon ECS) cluster with the A WS Fargate launch type to run the containers. Use target tracking to scale automatically based on demand.",
        "B": "Store container images in an A mazon Elastic Container Registry (A mazon ECR) repository. Use an A mazon Elastic Container Service (A mazon ECS) cluster with the A mazon EC2 launch type to run the containers. Use target tracking to scale automatically based on demand.",
        "C": "Store container images in a repository that runs on an A mazon EC2 instance. Run the containers on EC2 instances that are spread across multiple A vailability Zones. Monitor the average CPU utilization in A mazon CloudWatch. Launch new EC2 instances as needed.",
        "D": "Create an A mazon EC2 A mazon Machine Image (A MI) that contains the container image. Launch EC2 instances in an A uto Scaling group across multiple A vailability Zones. Use an A mazon CloudWatch alarm to scale out EC2 instances when the average CPU utilization threshold is breached."
      },
      "correct_answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Store container images in an A mazon Elastic Container Registry (A mazon ECR) repository. Use an A mazon Elastic Container Service (A mazon ECS) cluster with the A WS Fargate launch type to run the containers. Use target tracking to scale automatically based on demand."
    },
    {
      "id": "164",
      "question": "A company has two applications: asender application that sends messages with payloads to be processed and aprocessing application intended to receive the messages with payloads. The company wants to implement an A WS service to handle messages between the two applications. The sender application can send about 1,000 messages each hour. The messages may take up to 2 days to be processed: If the messages fail to process, they must be retained so that they do not impact the processing of any remaining messages. Which solution meets these requirements and is the MOST operationally eficient?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Set up an A mazon EC2 instance running a Redis database. Configure both applications to use the instance. Store, process, and delete the messages, respectively.",
        "B": "Use an A mazon Kinesis data stream to receive the messages from the sender application. Integrate the processing application with the Kinesis Client Library (KCL).",
        "C": "Integrate the sender and processor applications with an A mazon Simple Queue Service (A mazon SQS) queue. Configure a dead-letter queue to collect the messages that failed to process.",
        "D": "Subscribe the processing application to an A mazon Simple Notification Service (A mazon SNS) topic to receive notiFications to process. Integrate the sender application to write to the SNS topic."
      },
      "correct_answer": "C",
      "explanation": "Integrate the sender and processor applications with an A mazon Simple Queue Service (A mazon SQS) queue. Configure a dead-letter queue to collect the messages that failed to process."
    },
    {
      "id": "165",
      "question": "A solutions architect must design a solution that uses A mazon Cloudfront with an A mazon S3 origin to store astatic website. The company\u2019s security policy requires that all website traffic be inspected by A WS WAF. How should the solutions architect comply with these requirements?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Configure an S3 bucket policy to accept requests coming from the A WS WAF A mazon Resource Name (A RN) only.",
        "B": "Configure A mazon CloudFront to forward all incoming requests to A WS WAF before requesting content from the S3 origin.",
        "C": "Configure a security group that allows A mazon CloudFront IP addresses to access A mazon S3 only. A ssociate A WS WAF to CloudFront.",
        "D": "Configure A mazon CloudFront and A mazon S3 to use an origin access identity (OAI) to restrict access to the S3 bucket. Enable A WS WAF on the distribution."
      },
      "correct_answer": "D",
      "explanation": "Configure A mazon CloudFront and A mazon S3 to use an origin access identity (OAI) to restrict access to the S3 bucket. Enable A WS WAF on the distribution."
    },
    {
      "id": "166",
      "question": "Organizers for aglobal event want to put daily reports online as static HTML pages. The pages are expected to generate millions of views from users around the world. The files are stored in an A mazon S3 bucket. A solutions architect has been asked to design an eficient and effective solution. Which action should the solutions architect take to accomplish this?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Generate presigned URLs for the files.",
        "B": "Use cross-Region replication to all Regions.",
        "C": "Use the geoproximity feature of A mazon Route 53.",
        "D": "Use A mazon CloudFront with the S3 bucket as its origin."
      },
      "correct_answer": "D",
      "explanation": "Use A mazon CloudFront with the S3 bucket as its origin."
    },
    {
      "id": "167",
      "question": "A company runs aproduction application on aFieet of A mazon EC2 instances. The application reads the data from an A mazon SQS queue and processes the messages in parallel. The message volume is unpredictable and often has intermittent traffic. This application should continually process messages without any downtime. Which solution meets these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Use Spot Instances exclusively to handle the maximum capacity required.",
        "B": "Use Reserved Instances exclusively to handle the maximum capacity required.",
        "C": "Use Reserved Instances for the baseline capacity and use Spot Instances to handle additional capacity.",
        "D": "Use Reserved Instances for the baseline capacity and use On-Demand Instances to handle additional capacity."
      },
      "correct_answer": "C",
      "explanation": "Use Reserved Instances for the baseline capacity and use Spot Instances to handle additional capacity."
    },
    {
      "id": "168",
      "question": "A security team wants to limit access to specific services or actions in all of the team\u2019s A WS accounts. A ll accounts belong to a large organization in A WS Organizations. The solution must be scalable and there must be a single point where permissions can be maintained. What should A solutions architect do to accomplish this?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Create an A CL to provide access to the services or actions.",
        "B": "Create a security group to allow accounts and attach it to user groups.",
        "C": "Create cross-account roles in each account to deny access to the services or actions.",
        "D": "Create a service control policy in the root organizational unit to deny access to the services or actions."
      },
      "correct_answer": "D",
      "explanation": "Create a service control policy in the root organizational unit to deny access to the services or actions."
    },
    {
      "id": "169",
      "question": "A company is concerned about the security of its public web application due to recent web attacks. The application uses an A pplication Load Balancer (A LB). A solutions architect must reduce the risk of DDoS attacks against the application. What should the solutions architect do to meet this requirement?",
      "options": {
        "A": "A dd an A mazon Inspector agent to the A LB.",
        "B": "Configure A mazon Macie to prevent attacks.",
        "C": "Enable A WS Shield A dvanced to prevent attacks.",
        "D": "Configure A mazon GuardDuty to monitor the A LB."
      },
      "correct_answer": "C",
      "explanation": "Enable A WS Shield A dvanced to prevent attacks."
    },
    {
      "id": "170",
      "question": "A company\u2019s web application is running on A mazon EC2 instances behind an A pplication Load Balancer. The company recently changed its policy, which now requires the application to be accessed from one specific country only. Which configuration will meet this requirement?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Configure the security group for the EC2 instances.",
        "B": "Configure the security group on the A pplication Load Balancer.",
        "C": "Configure A WS WAF on the A pplication Load Balancer in a VPC.",
        "D": "Configure the network A CL for the subnet that contains the EC2 instances."
      },
      "correct_answer": "C",
      "explanation": "Configure A WS WAF on the A pplication Load Balancer in a VPC."
    },
    {
      "id": "171",
      "question": "A company provides an A PI to its users that automates inquiries for tax computations based on item prices. The company experiences a larger number of inquiries during the holiday season only that cause slower response times. A solutions architect needs to design a solution that is scalable and elastic. What should the solutions architect do to accomplish this?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Provide an A PI hosted on an A mazon EC2 instance. The EC2 instance performs the required computations when the A PI request is made.",
        "B": "Design a REST A PI using A mazon A PI Gateway that accepts the item names. A PI Gateway passes item names to A WS Lambda for tax computations.",
        "C": "Create an A pplication Load Balancer that has two A mazon EC2 instances behind it. The EC2 instances will compute the tax on the received item names.",
        "D": "Design a REST A PI using A mazon A PI Gateway that connects with an A PI hosted on an A mazon EC2 instance. A PI Gateway accepts and passes the item names to the EC2 instance for tax computations."
      },
      "correct_answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Design a REST A PI using A mazon A PI Gateway that accepts the item names. A PI Gateway passes item names to A WS Lambda for tax computations.\n "
    },
    {
      "id": "172",
      "question": "A solutions architect is creating a new A mazon Cloudfront distribution for an application. Some of the information submitted by users is sensitive. The application uses HTTPS but needs another layer of security. The sensitive information should.be protected throughout the entire application stack, and access to the information should be restricted to certain applications. Which action should the solutions architect take?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Configure a CloudFront signed URL.",
        "B": "Configure a CloudFront signed cookie.",
        "C": "Configure a CloudFront Field-level encryption proFile.",
        "D": "Configure CloudFront and set the Origin Protocol Policy setting to HTTPS Only for the Viewer Protocol Policy."
      },
      "correct_answer": "D",
      "explanation": "A solutions architect is creating a new A mazon CloudFront distribution for an application. Some of the information submitted by users is sensitive. The application uses HTTPS but needs another layer of security. The sensitive information should.be protected throughout the entire application stack, and access to the information should be restricted to certain applications.\nWhich action should the solutions architect take? \n\n    A. Configure a CloudFront signed URL.\n    B. Configure a CloudFront signed cookie.\n    C. Configure a CloudFront field-level encryption profile.\n    D. Configure CloudFront and set the Origin Protocol Policy setting to HTTPS Only for the Viewer Protocol Policy."
    },
    {
      "id": "173",
      "question": "A gaming company hosts abrowser-based application on A WS. The users of the application consume a large number of videos and images that are stored in A mazon S3. This content is the same for all users. The application has increased in popularity, and millions of users worldwide accessing these media files. The company wants to provide the files to the users while reducing the load on the origin. Which solution meets these requirements MOST cost-effectively?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Deploy an A WS Global A ccelerator accelerator in front of the web servers.",
        "B": "Deploy an A mazon CloudFront web distribution in front of the S3 bucket.",
        "C": "Deploy an A mazon ElastiCache for Redis instance in front of the web servers.",
        "D": "Deploy an A mazon ElastiCache for Memcached instance in front of the web servers."
      },
      "correct_answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Deploy an A mazon CloudFront web distribution in front of the S3 bucket."
    },
    {
      "id": "174",
      "question": "A company has a multi-tier application that runs six front-end web servers in an A mazon EC2 A uto Scaling group in a single A vailability Zone behind an A pplication Load Balancer (A LB). A solutions architect needs to modify the infrastructure to be highly available without modifying the application. Which architecture should the solutions architect choose that provides high availability?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Create an A uto Scaling group that uses three instances across each of two Regions.",
        "B": "Modify the A uto Scaling group to use three instances across each of two A vailability Zones.",
        "C": "Create an A uto Scaling template that can be used to quickly create more instances in another Region.",
        "D": "Change the A LB in front of the A mazon EC2 instances in a round-robin conFiguration to balance traffic to the web tier."
      },
      "correct_answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Modify the A uto Scaling group to use three instances across each of two A vailability Zones."
    },
    {
      "id": "175",
      "question": "A n ecommerce company has an order-processing application that uses A mazon A PI Gateway and an A WS Lambda function. The application stores data in an A mazon A urora PostgreSQL database. During arecent sales event, asudden surge in customer orders occurred. Some customers experienced timeouts, and the application did not process the orders of those customers. A solutions architect determined that the CPU utilization and memory utilization were high on the database because of a large number of open connections. The solutions architect needs to prevent the timeout errors while making the least possible changes to the application. Which solution will meet these requirements?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Configure provisioned concurrency for the Lambda function. Modify the database to be a global database in multiple A WS Regions.",
        "B": "Use A mazon RDS Proxy to create a proxy for the database. Modify the Lambda function to use the RDS Proxy endpoint instead of the database endpoint.",
        "C": "Create a read replica for the database in a different A WS Region. Use query string parameters in A PI Gateway to route traffic to the read replica.",
        "D": "Migrate the data from A urora PostgreSQL to A mazon DynamoDB by using A WS Database Migration Service (A WS DMS). Modify the Lambda function to use the DynamoDB table."
      },
      "correct_answer": "A",
      "explanation": "solutions architect determined that the CPU utilization and memory utilization were high on the database because of a large number of open connections. The solutions architect needs to prevent the timeout errors while making the least possible changes to the application.\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?\nB. Use A mazon RDS Proxy to create a proxy for the database. Modify the Lambda function to use the RDS Proxy endpoint instead of the database endpoint."
    },
    {
      "id": "176",
      "question": "A n application runs on A mazon EC2 instances in private subnets. The application needs to access an A mazon DynamoDB table. What is the MOST secure way to access the table while ensuring that the traffic does not leave the A WS network?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Use a VPC endpoint for DynamoDB.",
        "B": "Use a NAT gateway in a public subnet.",
        "C": "Use a NAT instance in a private subnet.",
        "D": "Use the internet gateway attached to the VPC."
      },
      "correct_answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Use a VPC endpoint for DynamoDB."
    },
    {
      "id": "177",
      "question": "A n entertainment company is using A mazon DynamoDB to store media metadata. The application is read intensive and experiencing delays. The company does not have staff to handle additional operational overhead and needs to improve the performance eficiency of DynamoDB without reconfiguring the application. What should A solutions architect recommend to meet this requirement?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Use A mazon ElastiCache for Redis.",
        "B": "Use A mazon DynamoDB A ccelerator (DAX).",
        "C": "Replicate data by using DynamoDB global tables.",
        "D": "Use A mazon ElastiCache for Memcached with A uto Discovery enabled."
      },
      "correct_answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Use A mazon DynamoDB A ccelerator (DAX). \n"
    },
    {
      "id": "178",
      "question": "A company\u2019s infrastructure consists of A mazon EC2 instances and an A mazon RDS DB instance in a single A WS Region. The company wants to back up its data in aseparate Region. Which solution will meet these requirements with the LEAST operational overhead?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Use A WS Backup to copy EC2 backups and RDS backups to the separate Region.",
        "B": "Use A mazon Data Lifecycle Manager (A mazon DLM) to copy EC2 backups and RDS backups to the separate Region.",
        "C": "Create A mazon Machine Images (A MIs) of the EC2 instances. Copy the A MIs to the separate Region. Create a read replica for the RDS DB instance in the separate Region.",
        "D": "Create A mazon Elastic Block Store (A mazon EBS) snapshots. Copy the EBS snapshots to the separate Region. Create RDS snapshots. Export the RDS snapshots to A mazon S3. Configure S3 Cross-Region Replication (CRR) to the separate Region."
      },
      "correct_answer": "C",
      "explanation": "A company\u2019s infrastructure consists of A mazon EC2 instances and an A mazon RDS DB instance in a single A WS Region. The company wants to back up its data in a separate Region.\nWhich solution will meet these requirements with the LEAST operational overhead? \n\n    A. Use A WS Backup to copy EC2 backups and RDS backups to the separate Region.\n    B. Use A mazon Data Lifecycle Manager (A mazon DLM) to copy EC2 backups and RDS backups to the separate Region.\n    C. Create A mazon Machine Images (A MIs) of the EC2 instances. Copy the A MIs to the separate Region. Create a read replica for the RDS DB instance in the separate Region.\n    D. Create A mazon Elastic Block Store (A mazon EBS) snapshots. Copy the EBS snapshots to the separate Region. Create RDS snapshots. Export the RDS snapshots to A mazon S3. Configure S3 Cross-Region Replication (CRR) to the separate Region."
    },
    {
      "id": "179",
      "question": "A solutions architect needs to securely store a database user name and password that an application uses to access an A mazon RDS DB instance. The application that accesses the database runs on an A mazon EC2 instance. The solutions architect wants to create asecure parameter in A WS Systems Manager Parameter Store. What should the solutions architect do to meet this requirement?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Create an IAM role that has read access to the Parameter Store parameter. A llow Decrypt access to an A WS Key Management Service (A WS KMS) key that is used to encrypt the parameter. A ssign this IAM role to the EC2 instance.",
        "B": "Create an IAM policy that allows read access to the Parameter Store parameter. A llow Decrypt access to an A WS Key Management Service (A WS KMS) key that is used to encrypt the parameter. A ssign this IAM policy to the EC2 instance.",
        "C": "Create an IAM trust relationship between the Parameter Store parameter and the EC2 instance. Specify A mazon RDS as a principal in the trust policy.",
        "D": "Create an IAM trust relationship between the DB instance and the EC2 instance. Specify Systems Manager as a principal in the trust policy."
      },
      "correct_answer": "A",
      "explanation": "A solutions architect needs to securely store a database user name and password that an application uses to access an A mazon RDS DB instance. The application that accesses the database runs on an A mazon EC2 instance. The solutions architect wants to create a secure parameter in A WS Systems Manager Parameter Store.\n\nWhat should the solutions architect do to meet this requirement?\n\n    A. Create an IAM role that has read access to the Parameter Store parameter. A llow Decrypt access to an A WS Key Management Service (A WS KMS) key that is used to encrypt the parameter. A ssign this IAM role to the EC2 instance.\n    B. Create an IAM policy that allows read access to the Parameter Store parameter. A llow Decrypt access to an A WS Key Management Service (A WS KMS) key that is used to encrypt the parameter. A ssign this IAM policy to the EC2 instance.\n    C. Create an IAM trust relationship between the Parameter Store parameter and the EC2 instance. Specify A mazon RDS as a principal in the trust policy.\n    D. Create an IAM trust relationship between the DB instance and the EC2 instance. Specify Systems Manager as a principal in the trust policy."
    },
    {
      "id": "180",
      "question": "A company is designing acloud communications platform that is driven by A PIs. The application is hosted on A mazon EC2 instances behind a Network Load Balancer (NLB). The company uses A mazon A PI Gateway to provide external users with access to the application through A PIs. The company wants to protect the platform against web exploits like SQL injection and also wants to detect and mitigate large, sophisticated DDoS attacks. Which combination of solutions provides the MOST protection? (Choose two.)",
      "options": {
        "A": "Use A WS WAF to protect the NLB.",
        "B": "Use A WS Shield A dvanced with the NLB.",
        "C": "Use A WS WAF to protect A mazon A PI Gateway.",
        "D": "Use A mazon GuardDuty with A WS Shield Standard",
        "E": "Use A WS Shield Standard with A mazon A PI Gateway."
      },
      "correct_answer": "BC",
      "explanation": "Use A WS Shield A dvanced with the NLB.\nC. Use A WS WAF to protect A mazon A PI Gateway."
    },
    {
      "id": "181",
      "question": "A company has alegacy data processing application that runs on A mazon EC2 instances. Data is processed sequentially, but the order of results does not matter. The application uses amonolithic architecture. The only way that the company can scale the application to meet increased demand is to increase the size of the instances. The company\u2019s developers have decided to rewrite the application to use amicroservices architecture on A mazon Elastic Container Service (A mazon ECS). What should A solutions architect recommend for communication between the microservices?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Create an A mazon Simple Queue Service (A mazon SQS) queue. A dd code to the data producers, and send data to the queue. A dd code to the data consumers to process data from the queue.",
        "B": "Create an A mazon Simple Notification Service (A mazon SNS) topic. A dd code to the data producers, and publish notiFications to the topic. A dd code to the data consumers to subscribe to the topic.",
        "C": "Create an A WS Lambda function to pass messages. A dd code to the data producers to call the Lambda function with a data object. A dd code to the data consumers to receive a data object that is passed from the Lambda function.",
        "D": "Create an A mazon DynamoDB table. Enable DynamoDB Streams. A dd code to the data producers to insert data into the table. A dd code to the data consumers to use the DynamoDB Streams A PI to detect new table entries and retrieve the data."
      },
      "correct_answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Create an A mazon Simple Queue Service (A mazon SQS) queue. A dd code to the data producers, and send data to the queue. A dd code to the data consumers to process data from the queue."
    },
    {
      "id": "182",
      "question": "A company wants to migrate its MySQL database from on premises to A WS. The company recently experienced a database outage that significantly impacted the business. To ensure this does not happen again, the company wants areliable database solution on A WS that minimizes data loss and stores every transaction on at least two nodes. Which solution meets these requirements?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Create an A mazon RDS DB instance with synchronous replication to three nodes in three A vailability Zones.",
        "B": "Create an A mazon RDS MySQL DB instance with Multi-A Z functionality enabled to synchronously replicate the data.",
        "C": "Create an A mazon RDS MySQL DB instance and then create a read replica in a separate A WS Region that synchronously replicates the data.",
        "D": "Create an A mazon EC2 instance with a MySQL engine installed that triggers an A WS Lambda function to synchronously replicate the data to an A mazon RDS MySQL DB instance."
      },
      "correct_answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Create an A mazon RDS MySQL DB instance with Multi-A Z functionality enabled to synchronously replicate the data."
    },
    {
      "id": "183",
      "question": "A company is building a new dynamic ordering website. The company wants to minimize server maintenance and patching. The website must be highly available and must scale read and write capacity as quickly as possible to meet changes in user demand. Which solution will meet these requirements?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Host static content in A mazon S3. Host dynamic content by using A mazon A PI Gateway and A WS Lambda. Use A mazon DynamoDB with on-demand capacity for the database. Configure A mazon CloudFront to deliver the website content.",
        "B": "Host static content in A mazon S3. Host dynamic content by using A mazon A PI Gateway and A WS Lambda. Use A mazon A urora with A urora A uto Scaling for the database. Configure A mazon CloudFront to deliver the website content.",
        "C": "Host all the website content on A mazon EC2 instances. Create an A uto Scaling group to scale the EC2 instances. Use an A pplication Load Balancer to distribute traffic. Use A mazon DynamoDB with provisioned write capacity for the database.",
        "D": "Host all the website content on A mazon EC2 instances. Create an A uto Scaling group to scale the EC2 instances. Use an A pplication Load Balancer to distribute traffic. Use A mazon A urora with A urora A uto Scaling for the database."
      },
      "correct_answer": "A",
      "explanation": "Host static content in A mazon S3. Host dynamic content by using A mazon A PI Gateway and A WS Lambda. Use A mazon DynamoDB with on-demand capacity for the database. Configure A mazon CloudFront to deliver the website content."
    },
    {
      "id": "184",
      "question": "A company has an A WS account used for software engineering. The A WS account has access to the company\u2019s on-premises data center through apair of A WS Direct Connect connections. A ll non-VPC traffic routes to the virtual private gateway. A development team recently created an A WS Lambda function through the console. The development team needs to allow the function to access a database that runs in a private subnet in the company\u2019s data center. Which solution will meet these requirements?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Configure the Lambda function to run in the VPC with the appropriate security group.",
        "B": "Set up a VPN connection from A WS to the data center. Route the traffic from the Lambda function through the VPN.",
        "C": "Update the route tables in the VPC to allow the Lambda function to access the on-premises data center through Direct Connect.",
        "D": "Create an Elastic IP address. Configure the Lambda function to send traffic through the Elastic IP address without an elastic network interface."
      },
      "correct_answer": "C",
      "explanation": "A company has an A WS account used for software engineering. The A WS account has access to the company\u2019s on-premises data center through a pair of A WS Direct Connect connections. A ll non-VPC traffic routes to the virtual private gateway.\nA development team recently created an A WS Lambda function through the console. The development team needs to allow the function to access a database that runs in a private subnet in the company\u2019s data center.\nWhich solution will meet these requirements?\n\n    A. Configure the Lambda function to run in the VPC with the appropriate security group.\n    B. Set up a VPN connection from A WS to the data center. Route the traffic from the Lambda function through the VPN.\n    C. Update the route tables in the VPC to allow the Lambda function to access the on-premises data center through Direct Connect.\n    D. Create an Elastic IP address. Configure the Lambda function to send traffic through the Elastic IP address without an elastic network interface."
    },
    {
      "id": "185",
      "question": "A company runs an application using A mazon ECS. The application creates resized versions of an original image and then makes A mazon S3 A PI calls to store the resized images in A mazon S3. How can A solutions architect ensure that the application has permission to access A mazon S3?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Update the S3 role in A WS IAM to allow read/write access from A mazon ECS, and then relaunch the container.",
        "B": "Create an IAM role with S3 permissions, and then specify that role as the taskRoleArn in the task deFinition.",
        "C": "Create a security group that allows access from A mazon ECS to A mazon S3, and update the launch conFiguration used by the ECS cluster.",
        "D": "Create an IAM user with S3 permissions, and then relaunch the A mazon EC2 instances for the ECS cluster while logged in as this account."
      },
      "correct_answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Create an IAM role with S3 permissions, and then specify that role as the taskRoleArn in the task definition."
    },
    {
      "id": "186",
      "question": "A company has aWindows-based application that must be migrated to A WS. The application requires the use of ashared Windows file system attached to multiple A mazon EC2 Windows instances that are deployed across multiple A vailability Zone: What should A solutions architect do to meet this requirement?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Configure A WS Storage Gateway in volume gateway mode. Mount the volume to each Windows instance.",
        "B": "Configure A mazon FSx for Windows File Server. Mount the A mazon FSx file system to each Windows instance.",
        "C": "Configure a file system by using A mazon Elastic File System (A mazon EFS). Mount the EFS file system to each Windows instance.",
        "D": "Configure an A mazon Elastic Block Store (A mazon EBS) volume with the required size. A ttach each EC2 instance to the volume. Mount the file system within the volume to each Windows instance."
      },
      "correct_answer": "B",
      "explanation": "A mazon FSx for Windows File Server provides a fully managed Windows file system that can be accessed by multiple EC2 instances. It is designed to provide shared file storage for Windows-based applications. It supports the SMB protocol, allowing Windows instances to mount the file system. A mazon FSx for Windows File Server is fully managed, highly available, and provides features like automatic backups and integration with A ctive Directory."
    },
    {
      "id": "187",
      "question": "A company is developing an ecommerce application that will consist of aload-balanced front end, acontainer-based application, and arelational database. A solutions architect needs to create a highly available solution that operates with as little manual intervention as possible. Which solutions meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "options": {
        "A": "Create an A mazon RDS DB instance in Multi-A Z mode.",
        "B": "Create an A mazon RDS DB instance and one or more replicas in another A vailability Zone.",
        "C": "Create an A mazon EC2 instance-based Docker cluster to handle the dynamic application load.",
        "D": "Create an A mazon Elastic Container Service (A mazon ECS) cluster with a Fargate launch type to handle the dynamic application load.",
        "E": "Create an A mazon Elastic Container Service (A mazon ECS) cluster with an A mazon EC2 launch type to handle the dynamic application load."
      },
      "correct_answer": "AD",
      "explanation": "A.  A mazon A thena for one-time queries. Use A mazon QuickSight to create dashboards for KPIs.\nD. A mazon Redshift for one-time queries. Use A mazon QuickSight to create dashboards for KPIs."
    },
    {
      "id": "188",
      "question": "A company uses A mazon S3 as its data lake. The company has a new partner that must use SFTP to upload data files. A solutions architect needs to implement a highly available SFTP solution that minimizes operational overhead. Which solution will meet these requirements?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Use A WS Transfer Family to conFigure an SFTP-enabled server with a publicly accessible endpoint. Choose the S3 data lake as the destination.",
        "B": "Use A mazon S3 File Gateway as an SFTP server. Expose the S3 File Gateway endpoint URL to the new partner. Share the S3 File Gateway endpoint with the new partner.",
        "C": "Launch an A mazon EC2 instance in a private subnet in a VPInstruct the new partner to upload files to the EC2 instance by using a VPN. Run a cron job script, on the EC2 instance to upload files to the S3 data lake.",
        "D": "Launch A mazon EC2 instances in a private subnet in a VPC. Place a Network Load Balancer (NLB) in front of the EC2 instances. Create an SFTP listener port for the NLB. Share the NLB hostname with the new partner. Run a cron job script on the EC2 instances to upload files to the S3 data lake."
      },
      "correct_answer": "A",
      "explanation": "A WS Transfer Family is a fully managed service that allows you to set up a secure file transfer protocol (SFTP) server for transferring files into and out of A mazon S3. With A WS Transfer Family, you can avoid the operational overhead of managing traditional SFTP servers. This solution provides a highly available SFTP service with minimal effort, and the data can be directly transferred to the S3 data lake."
    },
    {
      "id": "189",
      "question": "A company needs to store contract documents. A contract lasts for 5 years. During the 5-year period, the company must ensure that the documents cannot be overwritten or deleted. The company needs to encrypt the documents at rest and rotate the encryption keys automatically every year. Which combination of steps should A solutions architect take to meet these requirements with the LEAST operational overhead? (Choose two.)",
      "options": {
        "A": "Store the documents in A mazon S3. Use S3 Object Lock in governance mode.",
        "B": "Store the documents in A mazon S3. Use S3 Object Lock in compliance mode.",
        "C": "Use server-side encryption with A mazon S3 managed encryption keys (SSE-S3). Configure key rotation.",
        "D": "Use server-side encryption with A WS Key Management Service (A WS KMS) customer managed keys. Configure key rotation.",
        "E": "Use server-side encryption with A WS Key Management Service (A WS KMS) customer provided (imported) keys. Configure key rotation."
      },
      "correct_answer": "BD",
      "explanation": "B. s3 object Lock in compliance mode enforces a \"Write Once, Read Many\" (WORM) model, preventing the objects (contract documents, in this case) from being deleted or overwritten for a specified retention period.\nD. Use server-side encryption with A WS Key Management Service (A WS KMS) customer managed keys. Configure key rotation.\nBy using A WS KMS customer managed keys, you can configure key rotation to automatically rotate encryption keys, meeting the requirement of rotating encryption keys every year."
    },
    {
      "id": "190",
      "question": "A company has a web application that is based on Java and PHP. The company plans to move the application from on premises to A WS. The company needs the ability to test new site features frequently. The company also needs a highly available and managed solution that requires minimum operational overhead. Which solution will meet these requirements?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Create an A mazon S3 bucket. Enable static web hosting on the S3 bucket. Upload the static content to the S3 bucket. Use A WS Lambda to process all dynamic content.",
        "B": "Deploy the web application to an A WS Elastic Beanstalk environment. Use URL swapping to switch between multiple Elastic Beanstalk environments for feature testing.",
        "C": "Deploy the web application to A mazon EC2 instances that are conFigured with Java and PHP. Use A uto Scaling groups and an A pplication Load Balancer to manage the website\u2019s availability.",
        "D": "Containerize the web application. Deploy the web application to A mazon EC2 instances. Use the A WS Load Balancer Controller to dynamically route traffic between containers that contain the new site features for testing."
      },
      "correct_answer": "B",
      "explanation": "Elastic Beanstalk allows you to perform blue-green deployments, which involve creating a new environment (green) with the updated code, testing it, and then swapping the URLs to direct traffic to the new environment. This enables you to test new features without affecting the production environment."
    },
    {
      "id": "191",
      "question": "A company has an ordering application that stores customer information in A mazon RDS for MySQL. During regular business hours, employees run one-time queries for reporting purposes. Timeouts are occurring during order processing because the reporting queries are taking along time to run. The company needs to eliminate the timeouts without preventing employees from performing queries. What should A solutions architect do to meet these requirements?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Create a read replica. Move reporting queries to the read replica.",
        "B": "Create a read replica. Distribute the ordering application to the primary DB instance and the read replica.",
        "C": "Migrate the ordering application to A mazon DynamoDB with on-demand capacity.",
        "D": "Schedule the reporting queries for non-peak hours."
      },
      "correct_answer": "A",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "192",
      "question": "A hospital wants to create digital copies for its large collection of historical written records. The hospital will continue to add hundreds of new documents each day. The hospital\u2019s data team will scan the documents and will upload the documents to the A WS Cloud. A solutions architect must implement a solution to analyze the documents, extract the medical information, and store the documents so that an application can run SQL queries on the data. The solution must maximize scalability and operational eficiency. Which combination of steps should the solutions architect take to meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "options": {
        "A": "Write the document information to an A mazon EC2 instance that runs a MySQL database.",
        "B": "Write the document information to an A mazon S3 bucket. Use A mazon A thena to query the data.",
        "C": "Create an A uto Scaling group of A mazon EC2 instances to run a custom application that processes the scanned files and extracts the medical information.",
        "D": "Create an A WS Lambda function that runs when new documents are uploaded. Use A mazon Rekognition to convert the documents to raw text. Use A mazon Transcribe Medical to detect and extract relevant medical information from the text.",
        "E": "Create an A WS Lambda function that runs when new documents are uploaded. Use A mazon Textract to convert the documents to raw text. Use A mazon Comprehend Medical to detect and extract relevant medical information from the text."
      },
      "correct_answer": "BE",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "193",
      "question": "A company is running abatch application on A mazon EC2 instances. The application consists of abackend with multiple A mazon RDS databases. The application is causing a high number of reads on the databases. A solutions architect must reduce the number of database reads while ensuring high availability. What should the solutions architect do to meet this requirement?",
      "options": {
        "A": "A dd A mazon RDS read replicas.",
        "B": "Use A mazon ElastiCache for Redis.",
        "C": "Use A mazon Route 53 DNS caching",
        "D": "Use A mazon ElastiCache for Memcached."
      },
      "correct_answer": "A",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "194",
      "question": "A company needs to run a critical application on A WS. The company needs to use A mazon EC2 for the application\u2019s database. The database must be highly available and must fail over automatically if adisruptive event occurs. Which solution will meet these requirements?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Launch two EC2 instances, each in a different A vailability Zone in the same A WS Region. Install the database on both EC2 instances. Configure the EC2 instances as a cluster. Set up database replication.",
        "B": "Launch an EC2 instance in an A vailability Zone. Install the database on the EC2 instance. Use an A mazon Machine Image (A MI) to back up the data. Use A WS CloudFormation to automate provisioning of the EC2 instance if a disruptive event occurs.",
        "C": "Launch two EC2 instances, each in a different A WS Region. Install the database on both EC2 instances. Set up database replication. Fail over the database to a second Region.",
        "D": "Launch an EC2 instance in an A vailability Zone. Install the database on the EC2 instance. Use an A mazon Machine Image (A MI) to back up the data. Use EC2 automatic recovery to recover the instance if a disruptive event occurs."
      },
      "correct_answer": "A",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "195",
      "question": "A company\u2019s order system sends requests from clients to A mazon EC2 instances. The EC2 instances process the orders and then store the orders in a database on A mazon RDS. Users report that they must reprocess orders when the system fails. The company wants aresilient solution that can process orders automatically if asystem outage occurs. What should A solutions architect do to meet these requirements?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Move the EC2 instances into an A uto Scaling group. Create an A mazon EventBridge (A mazon CloudWatch Events) rule to target an A mazon Elastic Container Service (A mazon ECS) task.",
        "B": "Move the EC2 instances into an A uto Scaling group behind an A pplication Load Balancer (A LB). Update the order system to send messages to the A LB endpoint.",
        "C": "Move the EC2 instances into an A uto Scaling group. Configure the order system to send messages to an A mazon Simple Queue Service (A mazon SQS) queue. Configure the EC2 instances to consume messages from the queue.",
        "D": "Create an A mazon Simple Notification Service (A mazon SNS) topic. Create an A WS Lambda function, and subscribe the function to the SNS topic. Configure the order system to send messages to the SNS topic. Send a command to the EC2 instances to process the messages by using A WS Systems Manager Run Command."
      },
      "correct_answer": "C",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "196",
      "question": "A company runs an application on a large Fieet of A mazon EC2 instances. The application reads and writes entries into an A mazon DynamoDB table. The size of the DynamoDB table continuously grows, but the application needs only data from the last 30 days. The company needs a solution that minimizes cost and development effort. Which solution meets these requirements?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Use an A WS CloudFormation template to deploy the complete solution. Redeploy the CloudFormation stack every 30 days, and delete the original stack.",
        "B": "Use an EC2 instance that runs a monitoring application from A WS Marketplace. Configure the monitoring application to use A mazon DynamoDB Streams to store the timestamp when a new item is created in the table. Use a script that runs on the EC2 instance to delete items that have a timestamp that is older than 30 days.",
        "C": "Configure A mazon DynamoDB Streams to invoke an A WS Lambda function when a new item is created in the table. Configure the Lambda function to delete items in the table that are older than 30 days.",
        "D": "Extend the application to add an attribute that has a value of the current timestamp plus 30 days to each new item that is created in the table. Configure DynamoDB to use the attribute as the TTL attribute."
      },
      "correct_answer": "D",
      "explanation": "D. Extend the application to add an attribute that has a value of the current timestamp plus 30 days to each new item that is created in the table. Configure DynamoDB to use the attribute as the TTL attribute."
    },
    {
      "id": "197",
      "question": "A company has aMicrosoft .NET application that runs on an on-premises Windows Server. The application stores data by using an Oracle Database Standard Edition server. The company is planning amigration to A WS and wants to minimize development changes while moving the application. The A WS application environment should be highly available. Which combination of actions should the company take to meet these requirements? (Choose two.)",
      "options": {
        "A": "Refactor the application as serverless with A WS Lambda functions running .NET Core.",
        "B": "Rehost the application in A WS Elastic Beanstalk with the .NET platform in a Multi-A Z deployment.",
        "C": "Replatform the application to run on A mazon EC2 with the A mazon Linux A mazon Machine Image (A MI).",
        "D": "Use A WS Database Migration Service (A WS DMS) to migrate from the Oracle database to A mazon DynamoDB in a Multi-A Z deployment.",
        "E": "Use A WS Database Migration Service (A WS DMS) to migrate from the Oracle database to Oracle on A mazon RDS in a Multi-A Z deployment."
      },
      "correct_answer": "BE",
      "explanation": "B. Rehost the application in A WS Elastic Beanstalk with the .NET platform in a Multi-A Z deployment.\nE. Use A WS Database Migration Service (A WS DMS) to migrate from the Oracle database to Oracle on A mazon RDS in a Multi-A Z deployment."
    },
    {
      "id": "198",
      "question": "A company runs acontainerized application on aKubernetes cluster in an on-premises data center. The company is using aMongoDB database for data storage. The company wants to migrate some of these environments to A WS, but no code changes or deployment method changes are possible at this time. The company needs a solution that minimizes operational overhead. Which solution meets these requirements?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Use A mazon Elastic Container Service (A mazon ECS) with A mazon EC2 worker nodes for compute and MongoDB on EC2 for data storage.",
        "B": "Use A mazon Elastic Container Service (A mazon ECS) with A WS Fargate for compute and A mazon DynamoDB for data storage",
        "C": "Use A mazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (A mazon EKS) with A mazon EC2 worker nodes for compute and A mazon DynamoDB for data storage.",
        "D": "Use A mazon Elastic Kubernetes Service (A mazon EKS) with A WS Fargate for compute and A mazon DocumentDB (with MongoDB compatibility) for data storage."
      },
      "correct_answer": "D",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "199",
      "question": "A telemarketing company is designing its customer call center functionality on A WS. The company needs a solution that provides multiple speaker recognition and generates transcript files. The company wants to query the transcript files to analyze the business patterns. The transcript files must be stored for 7 years for auditing purposes. Which solution will meet these requirements?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Use A mazon Rekognition for multiple speaker recognition. Store the transcript files in A mazon S3. Use machine learning models for transcript File analysis.",
        "B": "Use A mazon Transcribe for multiple speaker recognition. Use A mazon A thena for transcript File analysis.",
        "C": "Use A mazon Translate for multiple speaker recognition. Store the transcript files in A mazon Redshift. Use SQL queries for transcript File analysis.",
        "D": "Use A mazon Rekognition for multiple speaker recognition. Store the transcript files in A mazon S3. Use A mazon Textract for transcript File analysis."
      },
      "correct_answer": "B",
      "explanation": ""
    },
    {
      "id": "200",
      "question": "A company hosts its application on A WS. The company uses A mazon Cognito to manage users. When users log in to the application, the application fetches required data from A mazon DynamoDB by using a REST A PI that is hosted in A mazon A PI Gateway. The company wants an A WS managed solution that will control access to the REST A PI to reduce development efforts. Which solution will meet these requirements with the LEAST operational overhead?",
      "options": {
        "A": "Configure an A WS Lambda function to be an authorizer in A PI Gateway to validate which user made the request.",
        "B": "For each user, create and assign an A PI key that must be sent with each request. Validate the key by using an A WS Lambda function.",
        "C": "Send the user\u2019s email address in the header with every request. Invoke an A WS Lambda function to validate that the user with that email address has proper access.",
        "D": "Configure an A mazon Cognito user pool authorizer in A PI Gateway to allow A mazon Cognito to validate each request."
      },
      "correct_answer": "D",
      "explanation": ""
    }
  ]
}